CAMILA **APARICIO**

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT



4 (647) 975-7248



camilaaparicioo@hotmail.com



in <u>linkedin.com/camilaaparicio</u>



www.camilaaparicio.com



github.com/camiaparicio

PROFILE

I am a front-end web developer with a passion for building responsive, accessible and engaging websites. My past experiences have cultivated my strong communication and problem solving skills. I have a constant desire and eagerness to keep learning and broadening my knowledge in web development.

Languages: English & Spanish

EDUCATION

Web Development Immersive **Bootcamp Certificate**

Juno College of Technology | 2021

Honours Bachelor of Applied Science in **Social Work**

University of Guelph-Humber | 2012-2016

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, jQuery, React, Firebase, Git & GitHub, Command Line, Restful APIs, Web Accessibility, Responsive Design, Pair Programing

PROJECTS

MEME IN A GIFFY

Github Repo \ Live Site HTML \ CSS \ REACT \ FIREBASE \ API

• A group-programmed application that allows users to generate their own memes by inputting text and saving their favourite results by using Firebase.

MOVIE SEARCHER

Github Repo \ Live Site

HTML \ CSS \ VANILLA JAVASCRIPT \ API

• A pair-programmed application that allows for users to search up movies using an API call to fetch data from the IMDB API.

E-COMMERCE SITE

Github Repo \ Live Site

HTML \ CSS \ JavaScript \ REACT \ API

• An e-commerce site entirely in React using the FakeStore API to fetch data. Users are able to filter through products via categories.

EXPERIENCE

PENSION TECHNICIAN

Morneau Shepell - Feb 2019 - Sept 2021

- Calculated and issued benefit payments in accordance with plan rules and legislation.
- Answered queries from clients, plan members and trustees, providing relevant information and appropriate follow-up.

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

First Republic Capital - Jan 2018 - Feb 2019

• Liaised with internal and external parties involved with the proceedings in preparation of private placements.

FRONT DESK COORDINATOR

Cactus Club Café - Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

• Coordinated and managed front desk team through effective guidance and strong communication skills in a professional manner in a high volume and demanding environment.